Dmitrii Kolesov

SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

69

69 476 25 78



davidbus1450@gmail.com



Garden Road, Central, Hong Kong

PROFILE

Ingenious, **Determined**, and **Self-motivated** senior software engineer with 9 years of professional experience who always works as a self-starter, with strong experience in the architecture, development, and maintenance of a wide variety of software. Experienced in the development of a diverse set of products and technologies, which includes e-commerce, NFT marketplaces, **blockchain** related products. Have great learning attitudes, and always trying to learn more and more.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

Upwork, Guru and Freelancer

May 2022 - Current

 Major in blockchain related projects like NFT marketplace, DeFi,and DAO projects as a Senior Blockchain &Fullstack developer.

SR BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Coincheck

Nov 2019 - May 2022

- Wrote smart contracts for decentralized applications and audited 100+ smart contracts.
 Strong experience with Unit Test and E2E Test.
- Functional specification reviews to ensure consistency and accuracy with the client's needs/
- Collaborated with external programmers to coordinate the delivery of 6 new software applications.
- Developed and deployed smart contracts for Token Bridge, DeFi,NFT marketplace,
 NFT minting, and Crypto exchange utilizing Web3.js, Solidity, and Rust.

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Moontek

Jun 2018 -Sep 2019

- Understand business drivers, goals/objectives, and opportunities and create innovative strategy/vision and solution roadmap/architecture for the implementation.
- Experienced with multiple Blockchain Technology platforms
- (Ethereum/Hyperledger/Ripple/Solana).
 Developed hundreds of smart contracts deployed on the main net, and audited 100+.
 Redesigned the company site and built it.

SKILLS

- Solidity
- Rust
- Ethereum
- Binance Smart Chain
- Solana
- DEX
- DeFi
- DAO
- Truffle, Hardhat
- Amazone Web Service
- Heroku / Netlify / Vercel
- Firebase
- Github / Gitlab

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE

California State University 2012 - 2016

INTERESTS

P2P, VIDEO GAME

BUNGE JUMPINIG